Guide to the Washington State University Capital Planning Building Files 1957-1998
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Vancouver Physical Plant Maintenance Shops - Schematic Design. 6/1998. / Architect: Zimmer Gunsul Frasca; Structural Engineer: Kramer GehlenMechanical: PAE Consulting Engineers, Inc.; Electrical: PAE Consulting Engineers, Inc.; Landscape Architect: Zim (Box 21)
- Vancouver - Multimedia Classroom Building - Schematic Design. 6/1998. / Architect: Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership,; Electrical: PAE Consulting Engineers, Inc.Landscape Architect: Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership; Civil Engineer: Kato and Warren, Inc. (Box 21)
- Vancouver - Phase 1 Campus Development - Schematic Design. Classroom Building Library Building; Student Services and Classroom Building 6504 or 6526; Physical Plant Building 1. 10/1993. / Architect: Zimmer Gunsul Frasca; Structural: Kramer GehlenMechanical (Box 21)
- Vancouver - Phase II Campus Development Schematic Design. Early Childhood/Education Facility. 12/1995. / Architect: Zimmer Gunsul Frasca, Partnership; Structural Engineer: Keramer Gehlen and AssociatesMechanical: PAE Consulting Engineers; Electrical Engin (Box 21)
- Vancouver - Phase II Campus Development - Preliminary Design. Campus Infrastructure Work. 3/1996. / Architect: Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership; Structural: Kramer Gehlen and AssociatesCivil: Kato and Warren Inc.,; Mechanical: PAE Consulting Engineers; Ele (Box 21)
- Vancouver - Cascades Volcano Observatory - United States Geological Survey. Conceptual Panning Submittal. 6/1996. / By: General Services Administration, United States Geological Survey United States Department of the Interior; Washington State University (Box 21)
- Vancouver - Phase II Academic Buildings - Predesign Study. Engineering Life Sciences Building; Multimedia/Electronic Communications Building. 5/1996. / Prepared By Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership (Box 21)
- Vancouver Campus Master Plan. 9/1992. / Prepared by: Zimmer Gunsul Frasca; Moyer/ReedParametrix, inc.; The JD White Company; The Basmaciyan Group; PAE Engineering; Geotechnical Resources Incorporated (Box 21)
- Vancouver Campus Master Plan Appendix: Wetlands, Wildfire and Fisheries Report; Geotechnical Investigation; Master Plan Utility Report; Master Plan Electrical Report; Master Plan Mechanical Report; Transportation; Technical Report. / Zimmer Gunsul Frasca (Box 21)
- Vancouver - A special Report to the Presidents and Regents from the ADVISORY COUNCIL VANCOUVER - Vancouver Long Range Planning Report. 3/1988. (Box 21)
- Vancouver and Clark College Bauer Hall - Second Phase Building Program - State Project # 88-030. 6/1988. (Box 21)
- Vancouver - Clark College Bauer Hall Phase II - State Project # 88-030. Project Manual for Construction Documents. 3/1989. / Gary Rogowski - Architect AIA; Structural: Kramer/Gehlen Associates Inc.Mechanical: Paraclete, PS; Electrical: Dean J. Alhay and A (Box 21)
- Vancouver - Draft Supplemental Environmental Impact Statement. 12/1992. / The JD White Company, Inc. (Box 22)
- Vancouver - Summary Master Plan. 7/1992. / Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership (Box 22)
- Vancouver - An Addition for The Southwest Washington Joint Center for Education and WSU At the Evergreen State College Building in Vancouver 1986 - 1987. / Andy Bremmeyer with Advisors; Don Heil, Robert Patton, and Dave ScottDr. George Condon, Director of WS (Box 22)
- Vancouver - Campus Infrastructure Preliminary Design Specifications. 2/1996. / Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership (Box 22)
- Vancouver - Campus Infrastructure Work - Phase II Development Construction Documents, WSU Review, Not for Construction. 5/1996. / Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership (Box 22)
- Vancouver - Mechanical and Electrical Calculation for the Phase II Campus Infrastructure Project and The Early Childhood/Education Facility Project. 8/1996. / PAE Consulting Engineers. Inc. (Box 22)
- Vancouver - Phase II Development Campus Infrastructure Work Construction Document Set. 1/1997. / Zimmmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership (Box 22)
- Vancouver - Early Childhood Education Facility. 7/1996. / Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership; Kramer Gehlen Associates Consulting Engineers/Structural/Civil (Box 22)
- Water System Plan Update. 12/1994. / Thomas, Dean and Hoskins, Inc. (Box 22)
- Water Research Center - Schematic Design Brochure. / Carlson and James Architects; Stingle and Atwood and AssociatesLyerla and Peden (Box 22)
- Waste Management Program Evaluation. Technical and Economic Feasibility Report - Appendix Section. 5/1990. / Doucet and Mainka, P.C. (Box 22)
- Wegner Hall - Specification (TRA Architecture Engineering Planning Interiors). General Work Project Manual Volume 1 of 3. 9/1979. / TRA Architecture Engineering Planning Interiors (Box 22)
- Wegner Hall - Specifications. Mechanical and Electrical Project Manual Volume 2 of 3. 9/1979. / TRA Architecture Engineering Planning Interiors (Box 22)
- Wegner Hall - Schedules - Project Manual Volume 3 of 3. 9/1979. / TRA Architecture Engineering Planning Interiors (Box 22)
- Wegner Hall - Library Addition - Schematic Design Brochure. / J. Kimball Barnard, AIA; Bovay Engineers, Inc., Structural Mechanical and Electrical (Box 22)
- Wegner Hall - Design Development Remodeling/Addition. 9/1978. (Box 22)
- Wegner Hall - Design Development Renovation/Addition. 10/1978. / TRA Architecture Engineering Planning Interiors (Box 22)
- Wegner Hall - Remodeling and Addition Building Program. 9/1977. (Box 22)
- Wenatchee - Tree Fruit Research Center - Office and Laboratory Building. 1966. / Fraley and Leighton Architects (Box 22)
- Wenatchee - Tree Fruit Research Center - USDA Addition. 1977. / Fraley and Leighton Architects (Box 22)
- Wilson Hall Remodeling - Schematic Design Brochure. 1971. / Architects: De Neff Deeble Barton Associates; Mechanical: Rice and LuhnElectrical: Wanless-Cook (Box 22)
- Wilson Compton Union Building Addition. 1966. / Architects: Maloney, Herrington, Greesz and Lund; Structural: Worthington, Skilling, Helle and JacksonMechanical and Electrical: Valentine, Fisher, and Tomlinson; Food Service Consultants: John R. Carlson Associat (Box 22)
- Wilmer Davis Hall - Food Services Facility - Design Development Documents. Proposed Alterations and Additions. 6/1970. / Architects: James and Hicks; Mechanical: Rice and LuhnElectrical: Wanless and Cook; Structural: Paul Panagakis; Food Service Consultants: J (Box 22)
- Womens Residence Hall - Schematic Design Brochure (Streit Perham). 1959. / Walker McGough and Trogdon Architects AIA (Box 22)
- Daggy Phase I Humanities Building. 4/1970. / Architects: Fred Bassetti and Company; Mechanical: Valentine, Fisher and TomlinsonElectrical: Beverly A. Travis and Associates; Theatrical Consultants: George C. Izenour and Associates; Acoustical Consultants. Robin (Box 23)
- Daggy Phase I Humanities/Speech Building - Building Program. (Box 23)
- Dana Hall Remodeling. 6/1973. / Architect: De Neff Deeble Barton Associates; Mechanical: Rice and LuhnElectrical: Wanless-Cook (Box 23)
- Athletic Facilities Study - Analysis of Existing Facilities! Improvements and Additions: 812S Martin Stadium; 0009 Hollingbery Field House; 372 Bailey Field; 171 Mooberry Track; 319C Stadium Way Tennis Courts; 013 Lower Soccer Fields; 365E WSU Golf Course (Box 23)
- AMID/Landscape Architecture Building Predesign Study. 5/1998. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 23)
- Consolidated Information Center (C.I.C.) - Project Manual Volume 1. 9/1995. / Integrus Architecture. P.S. (Box 23)
- Consolidated Information Center (C.I.C.) - Project Manual Volume 2. 9/1995. / Integrus Architecture, P.S. (Box 23)
- Campus infrastructure and Road improvements - Phase I. Schematic Design Brochure. 1/1998. / KPFF Consulting Engineers, Prime Civil Engineer; Wood/Harbinger, Mechanical/ElectricalC3 Management Group, Cost Estimator; White Shield, Surveyor/Geologist (Box 23)
- Carpenter Hall Renewal Building Program. 7/1987, 1/1988. (Box 23)
- Chemical Storage Building Environmental Health Services Facility. 5/1994. / Bovay Northwest, Inc. (Box 23)
- Cleveland Hall Renovation - Value Engineering Study. 6/1927. / Roen Associates (Box 23)
- Elevator Planning - Independent Counsel for Elevators in New Construction or Modernization "old". / Charles W. Lerch and Associates - Elevator Consulting and Engineers (Box 23)
- Hazardous Waste Facility - Dangerous Waste Permit WADO 0414853301. Chemical Storage Facility, Incinerator Basement, Hazardous Waste Treatment and Waste Water Discharge Facility. 9/1989. / Bovay Northwest Inc. (Box 24)
- Hazardous, Pathological, and Radiological Waste Handling Facilities. Building Program - Physical Plant Draft,. 11/1991. / Parametrix, Inc. (Box 24)
- Hydrogeologic Investigation of the Proposed Coal Ash Disposal Facility. Physical Plant, Parametrix, Final Report. 12/1991. / Parametrix, Inc. (Box 24)
- Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education - Joint Eastern Washington State College. Capital Budget Requests. 1977-1979. / Walker McGough Foltz Lyerla (Box 24)
- Records, Maintenance Materials Storage and Recycling - Project Manual. Phase I, Re - Bid Specifications, Archos Corporation. 10/1994. / Archos Corporation (Box 24)
- Records Maintenance, Material, Storage - Schematic Design, Inactive Records, Maintenance Materials Storage and Recycle Building: Phase I. 12/1992. / Archos Corporation (Box 24)
- Records, Maintenance Materials Storage, and Recycling Building - Phase I Building Program. 8/1991. (Box 24)
- Storm and Sanitary Sewer System Study - Physical Plant (Where is it located?). 8/1990. / CH2M Hill Engineers Planners Economists Scientists (Box 24)
- Student Services Addition - Project Manual Volume I Divisions 0 - 7 (Lighty Student Services). 9/1993. / Mahlum and Nordfors McKinley Gordon (Box 24)
- Student Services Addition - Project Manual Volume II Divisions 8 - 16 (Lighty Student Services). 9/1993. / Mahlum and Nordfors McKinley Gordon (Box 24)
- Stadium Way Programming Analysis - Draft Report. / KPFF Consulting Engineers (Box 24)
- Bohler Gymnasium Addition - Predesign Study. 10/1992. / Sasaki Associates, Inc.; Stewart Associates (Box 25)
- Bohler Gymnasium Renovation - Predesign Study. 6/1994. / Sasaki Associates, Inc.; Stewart Associates - Predesign Consultant (Box 25)
- Bohler Gymnasium Renovation - Capital Project Review Submittal. Allotment Request for Construction. 6/1994. / Prepared BY: WSU Department of Facilities Development (Box 25)
- Animal Science Building - Predesign Study. 7/1992. / MBT Associates - Predesign Consultants (Box 25)
- Engineering/Life Sciences Building. Multimedia/Electronic Communications Building. Phase II Academic Buildings - Predesign Study - Vancouver. 5/1996. / Zimmer Gunsul Frasca (Box 25)
- Chemical Storage Building. Environmental Health Services Facility - Predesign Study. 5/1994. / Bovay Northwest - Predesign Consultant (Box 25)
- Phase II Science Hall Remodeling - Building Program (Murrow East). 12/1985. (Box 25)
- Veterinary Teaching Hospital - Building Program (Bldg. Communication, Value Engineering Report, Physical Plant, Schedule and Equipment) +Slides and Pictures. 1991. / De Neff Deeble Barton Associates Architects and Planners (Box 26)
- WSU Tri-Cities Early Building Specifications. 1964 -1981. (Box 26)
- TriCities University Center Addition - Project Manual. 2/1990. / McKinley Architects - Volume 1 Divisions 0 - 7 (Box 26)
- TriCities University Center Addition - Project Manual. / McKinley Architects - Volume 2 Divisions 8 - 16 (Box 26)
- TriCities University Center Addition - Addendum No. 3. 3/1990. / McKinley Architects (Box 26)
- TriCities University Center Addition - Project Manual As Built. / McKinley Architects - Volume 1 Divisions 0 - 14 (Box 26)
- Animal Disease Biotechnology Facility - Project Data Base - Second Submittal. 11/1993. / Northwest Architectural Company; Wyatt - Jaykim Engineers - SurveyorsGifford Consulting Northwest - Geotechnical Consultants to Wyatt - Jaykim; C3 Management Group (Box 27)
- ADBF - Responses to Review Comments - (These annotated comments accompany the Bid Set, responding to review comments from earlier submittals.). 7/1994. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 27)
- ADBF - Area Comparison/Cost estimate/Mechanical Calculations/Fire Protection Calculations/Electrical Calculations - Final Review Submittal. 2/1994. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 27)
- ADBF - Schematic Design Slides - BD. Of Regents Presentation. (Box 27)
- ADBF - Energy Conservation Report and Life Cycle Cost Analysis. 3/1993. / Northwest Architectural Company - Architects/Engineers (Box 27)
- ADBF - Fixed Equipment - Third Submittal. 12/1993. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 27)
- ADBF - A landmark facility dedicated to serving the state of Washington. the Western Region. and the Nation. College of Veterinary; Medicine Facility Program Goals/Financial Summary of ADBF; Grants, Licenses and Selected Refereed Publications in 93 and 94. 2/ (Box 27)
- ADBF Slide - College of Veterinary Medicine. (Box 27)
- ADBF NAC Aerial Drawing of CVM (photo and slide). 7/1994. (Box 27)
- ADBF - College of Veterinary Medicine - Design Development Manual Volume II. Structural/Mechanical/Electrical Calculations. 11/1992. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 27)
- ADBF College of Veterinary Medicine - Design Development Manual - Volume I. Project Description/Cost Estimate/Equipment Schedule/Code Analysis. 11/1992. / Northwest Architectural Company; Structural Design NorthwestGerard and Associates - Mechanical; Crei (Box 27)
- ADBF - Cost Estimate - Third Submittal - Cost Estimate. 12/1993. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 27)
- ADBF - Krieger Steel Products - Brochure Material. 12/1990. (Box 27)
- ADBF - Water Saver Faucet Co. - Brochure Material: Laboratory and Hospital Faucet Fixtures; Emergency Eye Wash and Shower Equipment. 7/1990. (Box 27)
- Animal Sciences Laboratory - Construction Documents Estimate Prepared For MBT. 5/1995. / Ackroyd - Cost Control Consultants (Box 27)
- Animal Sciences Laboratory - Won - Door Corporation (fire guard) Brochure Material. 8/1991. (Box 27)
- Animal Sciences Laboratory Building - Value Engineering Services. 8/1994. / EFT - Architects/Planners/Project Managers (Box 27)
- Animal Sciences Laboratory Building - Value Engineering Study Proposal. 8/1994. / Meng Associates, Analysis Group - Architecture Planning/Value Engineering/Construction Research (Box 27)
- Asbestos Removal Plans - Alpha Engineering Group, Inc. (Box 27)
- Beasley Performing Arts Coliseum - Asbestos Removal and Abatement Specifications. 4/1992. / By the Board of Regents - Physical Plant Department (Box 27)
- Beasley Performing Arts Coliseum - Asbestos Survey Report for the Department of Physical Plant. / Alpha Engineering Group, Inc. (Box 27)
- Bohler Addition - Summary of Field and Laboratory Test Results File: WASUMI - M9601 A/ Contract 12254. 8/1997. / Strata Geotechnical Engineering and Materials Testing (Box 27)
- Bohler Gym Addition/Renewal - Statement of Qualifications. 10/1991. / Sasaki Associates, Inc. (Box 27)
- Bohler Gym Addition - Revised OFM Predesign Submittal. / Prepared for Sasaki Associates, Inc. By C3 Management Group (Box 27)
- Bohler Gymnasium Addition - 50% Design Development Value Engineering! Workbook and Preliminary Idea Listing Test and Screen Alternatives - Optimize Total Costs and Total Performance. / Ehninger Fetzer Tholen - Architects/Planners/Project Managers (Box 27)
- Bohler Gymnasium Remodel - OFM Predesign Submittal. 5/1994. / C3 Management Group, Inc. (Box 27)
- Bohler Gymnasium Addition - Life Cycle Cost Analysis (Report Some Plans Included). 2/1995. / Notkin Engineering, inc. (Box 27)
- Chemistry Building Cost Estimate Analysis. 3/1986. / Brooks Hensley Creager Architects (Box 27)
- Chemistry Building - Program Statement. 3/1984. (Box 27)
- Chemistry Building - Design Development. Pedestrian Corridor Development of College Avenue From Library Road to Stadium Way. / Brooks Hensley Creager Architects (Box 27)
- Child Care Playground - Project Manual. 4/1994. / Architect: The Tsang Partnership. inc.; Landscape Architect: Douglas H. Tuma, ASLA (Box 27)
- Child Care Center - Building Program. 6/1991. (Box 27)
- Child Care Facility Playground - Specifications. 4/1994. / Architect: The Tsang Partnership, Inc.; Landscape Architect: Douglas H. Tuma, ASIA (Box 27)
- Request for Proposal, Strategic Partner in Communications - WSU Systems and Computing. 4/1991. (Box 28)
- University Center/Classroom Auditoria Building - Predesign Study. 5/1992. / Predesign Consultant: The Callison Partnership. Ltd. (Box 28)
- University Center - Site Considerations. 5/1992. / Burke/Lee A Joint Venture, Architects, Planners and Landscape Architects (Box 28)
- Communication Infrastructure Renewal Project - Submitted July 1, 1993 to the CIR Review Team for Approval of the Format, Approval Requested Zone 2 - Sloan MCF - Communications Closet Drawings. 7/1993. / JWP information Systems Network Integration Services (Box 28)
- Composting Facility - Preliminary Design Report Draft - Project #0901-001.01. 3/1994. / Prepared for WSU by EMCON Northwest (Box 28)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Phase II Cost Estimate and Area Comparison Charts - Schematic Design Phase. 4/1992. / The BJSS Group - Architects and Planners AIA (Box 28)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Phase II Construction Documents - Cost Estimate. 2/1993. / The BJSS Group - Architects and Planners, AIA (Box 28)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Phase II Addendum No. 2. 6/1993. / The BJSS Group (Box 28)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Phase II Addendum No. 3. / The BJSS Group (Box 28)
- Kruegel Hall McAllister Hall Neill Hall - Photo Album. 4/1957. (Box 28)
- Mechanical Engineering Laboratory - Hazardous Materials Survey AGRA E and Es Job No. 12-1195-00. 8/1994. / AGRA Earth and Environmental (Box 28)
- ETRL - Preliminary Environmental Assessment. 5/1994. / Prepared by Hart Crowser for The Callison Partnership (Box 28)
- ETRL - Pre-Design Building Program Draft - College of Engineering and Architecture. 7/1992. (Box 28)
- ETRL - Value Engineering Study. 5/1994. / Meng Analysis Group - Value Engineering/Construction Research (Box 28)
- ETRL - Value Engineering Study - (different from above). 5/1994. / Meng Associates - Analysis Group/Architecture/Planning/Value Engineering/Construction Research (Box 28)
- McAllister/Kruegel Residence Halls Consultant Agreement No. 11063. 2/1993. / SCM Consultants, Inc. Architects and Engineers (Box 28)
- McAllister/Kruegel Residence Halls Consultant Agreement No. 11063 - Part C Structural Analysis. 2/1993. / SCM Consultants Inc. Architects and Engineers (Box 28)
- Fulmer Hall/Fulmer Annex Renewal - Budget Estimate. 6/1993. / Mahlum and Nordfor McKinley Gordon (Box 28)
- Fulmer Hall - Mckinley Gordon Architects Statement of Qualifications. 3/1993. (Box 28)
- Fulmer Hall/Fulmer Annex - Operations and Maintenance Plan for Asbestos. 3/1994. / RZA AGRA, Inc. (Box 28)
- Fulmer Hall/Fulmer Annex Renovation Project - Consultant Roster Registration Environmental Consulting Services and Proposal for the Renovation Project. 11/1993. / Hart Crowser - Earth and Environmental Technologies (Box 28)
- Fulmer Hall/Fulmer Annex Renewal - Lab Layout Drawings for user Group Meetings. 11/1993. / Mahlum and Nordfors McKinley Gordon (Box 28)
- Fulmer Annex Renewal - Energy Conservation Report. 4/1994. / Prepared by Riley Engineering, Inc. Mahlum and Nordfors Mckinley Gordon (Box 28)
- Glenn Terrell Friendship Mall and Extended Areas - Technical Report. 5/1987. / By Landscape Architecture Students in Landscape Architecture 361; Department of Horticulture and Landscape Architecture (Box 28)
- Glenn Terrell Friendship Mall - Schematic Design Brochure. / Design Team Catherin Howett/George Trakas; A Partnership Project of WSU and the WSU Arts Commission (Box 28)
- Greenhouse Replacements - Design Development/Puyallup WWREC with Slides Included. 2/1995. / Stafford Harris, Inc. (Box 28)
- Hazardous Waste Sites Phase II - Preliminary Construction Budget Estimate. 1/1994. / Bovay Northwest Inc. (Box 28)
- Chemical Waste Collection Sites - Schematic Design Brochure. (Box 28)
- Eastlick Hall/Wegner Hall/Engineering Complex/Silver Recovery Units. 11/1994. / Bovay Northwest Inc. (Box 28)
- Chemical Storage Building/Environmental Health Services Facility - Predesign Study (DRAFT). 4/1994. / Bovey Northwest, Inc. (Box 28)
- Hill Residence Halls - Condition Survey/Review - Stevens and McCroskey Halls. Duarte Bryant Architecture - Statement of Qualifications. 3/1995. (Box 29)
- Stevens Hall Dormitory - Exterior Renovation - Design Submittal. Lateral Study/Outline Specifications/Cost Estimate. 12/1992. / Duarte Bryant Architecture (Box 29)
- Stevens Hall Dormitory - Exterior Restoration - Building Survey. 8/1992. / Duarte Bryant Architecture (Box 29)
- Heald Hall - Rebar Study (Reinforcing Investigation). 7/1993. / Miller Hull Partnership (Box 29)
- Heald Hall - Expanded Options Study. 8/1995. / The Miller/Hull Partnership (Box 29)
- Heald Hall Renewal - Predesign Phase Proposal. 3/1992. / The Miller/Hull Partnership (Box 29)
- Heald Hall Renewal - Options Phase Document. 6/1992. / The Miller/Hull Partnership (Box 29)
- Holland Library Addition - Design Development. / ALSC Architects/ Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership - Design Architect; Structural: Structural Design NorthwestMechanical: Riley Engineering; Electrical: Doyle Engineering; Civil: Wyatt - Jaykim (Box 29)
- Libraries - A Guide to Spacesaver High - Density Compact Storage Systems for the Library Environment The Space Saver Group. (Box 29)
- Holland Library Renewal - Project Scope Development. 1/1994. / ALSC Architects, P.S. (Box 29)
- Holland Library Addition - Design Development Cost Estimate. 2/1990. / ALSC Architects/Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership - Design Architect (Box 29)
- Holland Library Addition - Holland Library Addition - Package No. 2. 8/1993. / Mortenson - The Construction Organization (Box 29)
- Holland Library Addition - Design Development/Cost Estimate. 1/1989. / C3Management Group, Inc. (Box 29)
- Library - An Assessment of Current and Projected Library Space Needs @ WSU. 3/1988. / P. Genie Trapp - Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
- ICNE - Yakima Permanent Facility - Proposed Site Study. Location: Between Glenn, Palmer and Prior Halls and the Brown Dental Clinic. 2/1994. / Integrus Architecture, P.S. (Box 29)
- ICNE Yakima Site Studies Log Project No. 93091. 1993. / SCM Consultant, Inc. (Box 29)
- Wheat Research Center - New Plant Growth. / Tan Boyle Heyamota Architects; Architects Design Group, Design ConsultantsPeden Petersen Lee, Structural Consultants; MW Consulting Engineers, Mechanical and Electrical Consultants; Ricard Carothers Associates (Box 29)
- Plant Growth Wheat Research Center - Schematic Design (Layouts). (Box 29)
- New Plant Growth - Wheat Research Center - Schematic Design Submittal. 11/1994. / Tan Boyle Heyamota/Architects Design Group (Box 29)
- New plant Growth Facility - Submittal of Qualifications. 5/1994. / Tan Boyle Heyamoto Architects/Architect Design Group (Box 29)
- Inactive Records, Maintenance Materials Storage, and Recycle Building: Phase 1 - Schematic Design. 12/1992. / Archos Corporation (Box 29)
- Records, Maintenance Materials Storage, and Recycling Building - Construction Document Submittal. 9/1993. / Archos Corporation (Box 29)
- Records, Maintenance Material Storage, and Recycling building - Phase I - First Design Submittal. 4/1992. / Archos Corporation (Box 29)
- Records, Maintenance Material Storage, and Recycling Building - Phase I - Revised Schematic Design Submittal. 10/1992. (Box 29)
- Records Storage and Recycle Building - Schematic Design Cost Estimate. 11/1992. / Archos Corporation/C3 Management Group, Inc. (Box 29)
- Records, Maintenance Materials Storage, and Recycling Building Phase I - Supplementary Building Program. 3/1992. / Archos Corporation (Box 29)